<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<compositeCheatsheet name="ModuleStudio Cheat Sheet">
   <taskGroup kind="sequence" name="Build software the easy way" skip="false">
      <intro>
         <description>
            This cheat sheet is a tutorial showing how to create applications with ModuleStudio.
         </description>
      </intro>
      <onCompletion>
         Now you have built a complete application by the simple use of model elements. <b>Great, isn&apos;t it?</b>
      </onCompletion>
      <task kind="cheatsheet" name="Start a new project" skip="true">
         <intro>
            In this lesson you learn how to create new projects by using a wizard.
         </intro>
         <onCompletion>
            Now that you have a project you can start moving around.
         </onCompletion>
         <param name="path" value="2_startproject.xml"></param>
      </task>
      <task kind="cheatsheet" name="Explore the environment" skip="true">
         <intro>
            Learn the basic elements of ModuleStudio and how to use them.
         </intro>
         <onCompletion>
            Now that you know the basic elements of ModuleStudio you are ready for building models.
         </onCompletion>
         <param name="path" value="3_environment.xml"></param>
      </task>
      <taskGroup kind="sequence" name="Describe application layers models" skip="false">
         <intro>
            Learn how the different editor types work and how they describe applications.
         </intro>
         <onCompletion>
            You learnt to know the different editor types and have a full model.
         </onCompletion>
         <task kind="cheatsheet" name="Define application settings" skip="false">
            <intro>
               This cheat sheet helps you to create a new model as a starting point for your own application.
            </intro>
            <onCompletion>
               It was shown what must be considered during modeling the application layer.
            </onCompletion>
            <param name="path" value="4_editorstart.xml"></param>
         </task>
         <task kind="cheatsheet" name="Modeling data layers" skip="false">
            <intro>
               This cheat sheet helps you to create a new model layer within your application.
            </intro>
            <onCompletion>
               Now the application's data structure has been defined.
            </onCompletion>
            <param name="path" value="5_editormodel.xml"></param>
         </task>
         <task kind="cheatsheet" name="Modeling controller layers" skip="false">
            <intro>
               This cheat sheet helps you to create a new controller layer within your application.
            </intro>
            <onCompletion>
               Now the controller details have been specified.
            </onCompletion>
            <param name="path" value="6_editorcontroller.xml"></param>
         </task>
         <task kind="cheatsheet" name="Modeling view layers" skip="true">
            <intro>
               This cheat sheet helps you to create a new view layer within your application.
            </intro>
            <onCompletion>
               Now the output layer has been described.
            </onCompletion>
            <param name="path" value="7_editorview.xml"></param>
         </task>
         <task kind="cheatsheet" name="Modeling workflows" skip="true">
            <intro>
               This cheat sheet helps you to customise your application workflows.
            </intro>
            <onCompletion>
               Now the application model contains individual workflows.
            </onCompletion>
            <param name="path" value="8_editorworkflow.xml"></param>
         </task>
      </taskGroup>
      <task kind="cheatsheet" name="Generating an application" skip="false">
         <intro>
            Model validation and how to generate code from it.
         </intro>
         <onCompletion>
            This lession has presented validation and shown how to generate code from your model.
         </onCompletion>
         <param name="path" value="9_generator.xml"></param>
      </task>
   </taskGroup>
</compositeCheatsheet>
