<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<introContent>
  	<extensionContent id="firststeps-top-left" style="css/style.css" name="First Steps Extension" path="firststeps/@">
		<group style-id="content-group" id="deguitemodulestudio-introLink-group">
       		<text>Here are some hints for getting into ModuleStudio smoothly.</text>
       		<text>Each application is being represented by a model. A model consists of two files: a domain model (*.mostapp) and the diagram model (*.mostdiagram). The first one is the important thing containing all information relevant for further processing like model-to-model and model-to-code transformations. The diagram information is only cosmetical and not neccessary. So if you want to exchange models, only the domain model is needed from which a new diagram model can be initialised.</text>
       		<text>Not all settings are directly embedded within the editor. To be able to set all fields refer to the "properties view" at the bottom right. There you can find an element named "domain" relating to a particular element with focus.</text>
       		<text>At first start with simple goals. Think about an application needing only three to five database tables (entity objects in the model editor). Keeping your application-specific logic simple helps to understand the architectural concepts of ModuleStudio.</text>
       		<text>You may have a look into some existing example models. Please refer to the project homepage where you can find according downloads.</text>
       	</group>
  	</extensionContent>
    <extensionContent id="firststeps-top-right" style="css/style.css" name="First Steps Extension" path="firststeps/@">
        <group style-id="content-group" id="deguitemodulestudio-introLink-group2">
            <text> </text>
            <text> </text>
        </group>
    </extensionContent>
    <extensionContent id="firststeps-bottom-left" style="css/style.css" name="First Steps Extension" path="firststeps/@">
        <group style-id="content-group" id="deguitemodulestudio-introLink-group3">
            <text>This preview version has several bugs. The following describes the critical ones I know and how to treat them.</text>
            <text>1. The domain models (*.mostapp) store their own file path so that this can assigned to the generator by the editor easily. In later versions of ModuleStudio this path will be checked and updated on opening a model. At the moment this path has to be modified manually with a text editor to make generation work properly, if the file location changes. The file path can be found in an attribute of the root element at the beginning of the model file.</text>
            <text>2. To ensure correct storage of your modeled information, you will have to save the main model once *before* you open any sub editors and add according content. This issue is inherited from a framework used by the ModuleStudio architecture. If it is not going to be solved within the next few months, the behaviour in ModuleStudio will be changed to enforce a save if needed before opening a subeditor. As soon as the main model has been saved, creating new sub models goes without problems.</text>
            <text>3. If you work with windows you have to place your models into a folder without spaces (e.g. D:\mymodels\). Otherwise generation will fail.</text>
            <text>4. The automatic update of ModuleStudio does not work correctly yet. So you will have to get new versions from the project homepage.</text>
        </group>
    </extensionContent>
    <extensionContent id="firststeps-bottom-right" style="css/style.css" name="First Steps Extension" path="firststeps/@">
    </extensionContent>
</introContent>