<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<introContent>
  	<extensionContent id="overview-top-left" style="css/style.css" name="Overview Extension" path="overview/@">
		<group style-id="content-group" id="deguitemodulestudio-introLink-group">
          	<text>ModuleStudio (MOST) is a generative architecture for the Zikula Application Framework. Based on principles of Model-Driven Software Development (MDSD) the creation of modules is being abstracted to a new level.</text>
          	<text>Replace coding by modeling and simplify your development!</text>
          	<text>Make your applications following all APIs, guidelines and recommendations automatically!</text>
       	</group>
   	</extensionContent>
    <extensionContent id="overview-top-right" style="css/style.css" name="Overview Extension" path="overview/@">
		<group style-id="content-group" id="deguitemodulestudio-introLink-group">
			<text>What are the advantages?</text>
			<text>    * development time/costs: avoid wasting weeks for schematical and architectural motivated code parts!</text>
			<text>    * maintainability: your software is a model - easily changeable and cheaply maintainable! No more efforts for getting your modules up to date for new versions!</text>
			<text>    * code quality: take profit from best practices and established patterns!</text>
			<text>    * architectural compliance: take most usage from powerful core frameworks and interfaces! No more unsecure and legacy extensions!</text>
			<text>    * reusability: share and modify your models! Do not make the same work twice!</text>
			<text>	  * understandibility: avoid having to learn programming rules and framework details! Develop with general terms independant from technical stuff!</text>
       	</group>
    </extensionContent>
    <extensionContent id="overview-bottom-left" style="css/style.css" name="Overview Extension" path="overview/@">
		<group style-id="content-group" id="deguitemodulestudio-introLink-group">
			<text> </text>
			<text> </text>
       	</group>
        <group style-id="content-group" id="deguitemodulestudio-introLink-group">
            <text>This quite early version of ModuleStudio contains only basic functionality, preparing further enhancements.</text>
            <text>MOST is intended to come in four different editions (CE, SE, PE, EE).</text>
            <text>Please use the support forums for questions, suggestions and other feedback.</text>
        </group>
    </extensionContent>
    <extensionContent id="overview-bottom-right" style="css/style.css" name="Overview Extension" path="overview/@">
        <group style-id="content-group" id="deguitemodulestudio-introLink-group">
            <text> </text>
            <text> </text>
        </group>
  	</extensionContent>
</introContent>