<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<introContent>
  	<extensionContent id="whatsnew-top-left" style="css/style.css" name="Whats New Extension" path="whatsnew/@">
        <group style-id="content-group" id="deguitemodulestudio-introLink-group052">
            <text>First version of user manual as reference (very simple version without interaction capabilities).</text>
            <text>Conversion of modeling language and generator for support of Doctrine 2.1 in the data layer.</text>
            <text>Updated to Eclipse 3.7 (Indigo).</text>
            <text>Fixed wrong property naming for feature license links on about page.</text>
            <text>Categories in the properties view for better overview of available properties.</text>
            <text>Description for all properties (visible in the status line at the bottom of the window).</text>
            <text>Activated multiline editor for generic documentation field.</text>
            <text>Support for other output formats (rss and atom feeds, csv list, xml markup).</text>
            <text>Support for language fields. These can be used like country, htmlcolour or ipaddress fields by activating the corresponding string field properties.</text>
            <text>Fixed wrong usage of Gettext in some form handler error messages.</text>
            <text>Repaired error on recurring update of relations.</text>
            <text>Bugfix for initialisation of boolean module variables.</text>
            <text>Whitelist with different redirect codes for flexible redirects in edit form handlers. Usable with redirectTo parameter in the edit links.</text>
            <text>Invisible array fields storing meta data information for upload fields.</text>
            <text>Validator classes for business entities providing common helper methods and possibility for custom checks.</text>
            <text>Ajax-based checks for direct feedback during editing content in unique fields.</text>
            <text>Flexible short url support based on a powerful routing, dynamic replacements and different configurations of sluggable behavior.</text>
            <text>Changed default value for license field from GPL to LGPL.</text>
            <text>Thumbnail images are now deleted together with their original images.</text>
            <text>Possibility to delete upload files without uploading a new file.</text>
            <text>Added html5 geolocation support for determination of default coordinates when using Geograhical behavior.</text>
            <text>Updated module layout to conform to default structure (main folders src and tests).</text>
            <text>Added colour picker support for string fields with htmlcolor set to true.</text>
            <text>Added tree hierarchy management for entities with nested sets.</text>
            <text>Manual editing of slugs (permalinks) if sluggableCanUpdate is set to true.</text>
            <text>Documentation cartridge has been removed as it will be contained in reporting.</text>
            <text>Generation does now automatically export all diagrams in various image formats.</text>
            <text>Direct usage of Doctrine_Pager instead of own selectCount method to retrieve the amount of affected records.</text>
            <text>The reports "documentation" and "modelInfos" are now multilingual.</text>
            <text>Support for all common core event listeners.</text>
            <text>Adapted newest core hook system changes.</text>
            <text>Changes for better support of i18n behavour.</text>
        </group>
        <group style-id="content-group" id="deguitemodulestudio-introLink-group051">
            <text>Editors: performance of live validation has been improved by closing a memory leak.</text>
            <text>Many bugfixes and corrections, especially for handling relations with Doctrine.</text>
            <text>Factories for business entities and collections: for each application a factory class is generated now, with which instantiation of new business objects is reduced to one line of code. This factory receives also the context from which the object has been asked for. For example this can be an action, a form handler or also a content type. Therewith it is possible to use different business classes depending on the context in specialisations of this factory class.</text>
            <text>Improved handling of user fields: if one has user fields in an entity, editing these fields is now done with an auto complete function in the forms.</text>
            <text>Handling upload fields with different possible settings in the model: you can now model different settings for upload fields, for example the allowed file extensions, the name of the subfolder storing the files or the scheme for naming uploaded files. The generator creates a complete upload handling from that, for images including support for the Thumbnail Module.</text>
            <text>Managing relations: the handling of relations has been overhauled completely, particularly in the edit forms. When editing an entity it is possible to choose, reference and manage (inline editing) other objects with auto complete fields. Each relation has a new property called "edit type" on modeling level. With that one can define on which side of the relation which actions should be possible.</text>
            <text>Improved ajax support: beside the Zikula.ImageViewer also the Zikula.UI library is used. When displaying and editing objects referenced objects are edited or embedded with it.</text>
            <text>Direct validation: when editing entities also client-side validation with validation.js is supported for some field types.</text>
            <text>Description of elements: each model element has a new field for functional documentation. In the main generator this information is only used for the application itself (module description), entities (description text at the top of list views) and their fields (Zikula.UI tooltips for labels in edit forms) at the moment.</text>
        </group>
  		<group style-id="content-group" id="deguitemodulestudio-introLink-group050">
            <text>Updated to Eclipse 3.6 Helios and according framework versions.</text>
            <text>Introduced new branding (new logo, splash screen and about screen).</text>
            <text>Comprehensive continuous Integration server setup to run different builds and tests automatically.</text>
            <text>Remote installer component for repository-based deployment and native OS integration.</text>
            <text>Incorporated display of rss feeds on web resources welcome page.</text>
            <text>Fixed meta model packages. This was a major refactoring due to an issue in earlier versions. Unfortunately this broke backwards compatibility. Luckily this won't happen again because in future those migrations will happen automatically due to the new versioning support (see next point).</text>
            <text>Added support for versioning metamodels and automatic migration of dependent models accordingly.</text>
            <text>Added new fields for defining the application type and the license of an application.</text>
            <text>Merged persistence and behaviour layers into one common data layer and removed some redundancies.</text>
            <text>Changed terminology to known terms of MVC.</text>
            <text>Prepared full support for all relevant functionalities of Doctrine in the data layer (column types, relationship types, validators, behaviors and event listeners).</text>
            <text>Added automatical creation of initial containers in the main editors diagram.</text>
            <text>Support for different generators, currently there are four cartridges: zClassic, zOO, documentation, reporting.</text>
            <text>Updated zClassic generator for Zikula 1.3.0 compliance (including support for Doctrine).</text>
            <text>Generator enhancements: Profiler, Precompiler, Php beautifier (source code formatter)</text>
            <text>Several minor fixes and additions.</text>
  		</group>
  	</extensionContent>
    <extensionContent id="whatsnew-top-right" style="css/style.css" name="Whats New Extension" path="whatsnew/@">
        <group style-id="content-group" id="news-web" label="MOST News">
            <contentProvider id="url=http://modulestudio.de/en/news.rss##welcome_items=20##no_news_url=http://modulestudio.de/en/news/##no_news_text=MOST news articles feed" pluginId="org.eclipse.ui.intro" class="org.eclipse.ui.intro.contentproviders.EclipseRSSViewer">
            </contentProvider>
        </group>
    </extensionContent>
    <extensionContent id="whatsnew-bottom-left" style="css/style.css" name="Whats New Extension" path="whatsnew/@">
    </extensionContent>
    <extensionContent id="whatsnew-bottom-right" style="css/style.css" name="Whats New Extension" path="whatsnew/@">
    </extensionContent>
</introContent>
